The public doesn't realize it, but
there's an evil lurking in Morioh.
It's like a silent disease slowly
ravaging our town from the inside out,
and every day more and
more lives are being taken.
What's worse, these killings have
gone completely unnoticed for years.
It's shocking to say the least, the
thought of it's downright chilling.
And we have no way of tracking down the
murderer, no matter how hard we try.
In fact, we still don't know how
many stand users are even in Morioh.
But people aren't worried about some
silent killer coming after them.
They're too preoccupied with
what they're having for dinner.
Everyone is completely blind to what's
going on outside their immediate view.
How can I only have 285 yen to my name?
Best I checked, I had 20,000 in savings!
12 yen!
I've got to work on my spending habits.
That 20,000 yen was for those
dope designer shoes I wanted.
What the hell else could I have
spent that amount of money on?
This is that crusty old man's fault!
He charged a hundred and thirty thousand
yen to my cart when he
bought that baby shit!
Though I have to admit the
geezer paid me back in full.
After that I got bit by
a mysterious spending
bug and my money sense
flew right out the window!
Maybe I'll get lucky and find a
thousand yen laying around somewhere,
though the odds of that are slim to none!
It's a disgusting roach.
That's a health code
violation if I ever seen one.
Is that a stand?
Great.
I got one man.
Where do you think you're going?
I was right, it's a stand!
Just when I thought this
day couldn't get any worse.
I don't know.
I don't know what I'm saying.
Where the hell is it going?
There's another one.
Dammit, what the hell are you?
You're about to get
slaughtered, you hear me?
Okuyasu!
Oh, heyya, Josuke.
Look, there's an enemy stand.
I'm gonna squash him to death.
Now there are two of them!
Yeah, I followed one of those little
pests all the way from the bank.
How did the one you're after attack you?
Well, he didn't actually attack me.
I was trying to buy a bottle
of Calpis water when suddenly
it popped out from under the
vending machine and took off!
That's all?
You mean it didn't try
to pick a fight with you?
Then why were you ranting about
wanting to squash it to death?
Cause the stupid little
bastard startled me so
bad I spilled the damn
water all over my uniform!
I want my money back, damn it! I got one!
Check it out!
Looks like another one of
those things joined the pack!
Whoa!
What the hell are these things?
There are so many of them!
They're like a pint-sized army!
Okuyasu, try not to
take this the wrong way,
but they kind of remind me
of your brother's stance.
Although, the fact that they're completely
ignoring us is giving me a bad feeling.
It's really creepy if you ask me. Yeah.
Stay alert.
The user is probably somewhere nearby.
Focus.
What?
It's money!
Oh, that's right, it took a one yen
coin from under the ATM at the bank.
As crazy as it is, I'm pretty sure
all those coins are the real deal.
Great work, everyone.
These are some good pickings.
Like they say, a yen
saved is a yen earned.
And counting all the money that
we've saved, this makes 5,000 yen.
As long as I have you by my side harvest,
I'll have everything I need to get by.
for the rest of my life.
Hey, do you see the way
he's talking to that stand.
He must be the user given
how chummy they are.
You're right.
Looks like another sorry chump
got tagged by the bow and arrow.
But going by his goofy attitude, it
doesn't seem like he wants to hurt anyone.
Grin.
Oh wow, this is so neat.
I had no clue other people
could see my harvest too.
Hey, guys, you can
really see it, can't you?
Yeah, so you know, they're
called stands. Wow.
I'm Josuke Higashikata, and
this here is Okuyasu Nijimura.
This means we're friends,
my very first friends!
Oh, right.
I guess I should tell you that
my name is Shigeki Oyangu.
I'm an eighth grader at
Burugaoka Middle School.
I weigh 110 kilograms and
my mommy and daddy call
me Shigechi because I'm
their special little man.
First they called me little
Shige, but now it's Shigechi.
I also have a pet turtle
and his name is Kinoto.
I was home the other
day and all of a sudden
I had the urge to find out whether the 41,
62, and 150 yen stamps tasted the same.
So I started licking them all over and
my mommy yelled at me something fierce.
This is a picture of my mommy,
the one who yelled at me.
A picture?
Holy shit, your mom is actually
pretty easy on the eyes.
What the hell?
So, uh, question for you.
These things are called Harvest, right?
Were they really the ones who
picked up all these coins?
You bet they were.
They got them from ditches in
the bottom of vending machines,
but I'm not a robber if
that's what you're thinking.
I already talked to the
Koban policeman about it.
He said it wasn't necessary to return
coin denominations less than 100 yen.
Nothing pees me off more
than doing bad things.
I don't think there's anything
bad about what you're doing.
If you ask me, you're
doing society a big favor.
It's no boatload of cash,
but you're taking forgotten funds and
putting them back into the Japanese economy.
You're doing great work here.
Really?
Do you mean it?
You think it's great?
Does that mean you think I'm great too?
Be honest.
Oh man, talk about being
hidden in plain sight.
I've got to hand it to the guy.
No one would ever think of
collecting money like this.
I'm so jealous.
He's a freakin' genius!
I...
I may have heard you incorrectly, but did
you happen to say I was a freakin' genius?
No one has ever said anything
like that to me before.
I've picked up 120,000
yen since I started...
120,000?!
But your kind words make me even happier.
Hey, you have 120,000
yen? Pretty good, huh?
And you scrounged together
all that money around Morioh?
Yep.
It's the only way to do things since
I never stepped foot out of town.
I could get lost and some Grip might
take advantage of my innocence, hee hee.
No fair.
I have 12 yen and he's rolling in it.
Aokuyasu, what's wrong
with your left foot?
Whoa, what in the world?
How did 350 in coins end up
hiding right under my foot?
You think this random money
might belong to Shigekio?
He should keep an eye on his dash.
You sneaky dick.
Oh, here you go.
I'll give you guys half.
Would that make you happy?
Huh?
We're each other's bestest
friends now, right?
We can all hang out and do cool things.
Really?
Do you mean it?
Lucky us!
No, wait.
This just isn't right.
You can't just hand over
your hard-earned money
to complete strangers
like it's nothing at all.
Okay, this time I'll put my back into it.
Go on, take it.
Half of all of this is yours.
That's what friends are for, isn't it?
Grunting and scrunching up your
face doesn't make it right!
Let's talk!
Can you excuse us for a second, Shigechi?
We need to chat.
Listen to me, Josuke.
Enough of the goody-goody shit.
If this turd boy wants to give us his
money, then who are we to turn him down?
Sorry, buddy, but my pride
won't allow me to do that.
It's just not right, okay?
As long as it's not some shitty disease,
I'll take whatever people are
given, so don't you judge!
All right, I get it.
I wasn't judging you.
Chill out.
Stop crying.
But you said...
Look, I know how you feel.
I'm not exactly raking
in yin myself, you know.
But never fear!
I just came up with a little idea
that'll put everyone's minds at ease.
Huh?
You really think it's possible
to make everyone happy?
Heh, just leave everything to me!
So, uh, Shigekyo.
Actually, uh, do you mind
if I call you Shigechi?
Oh, I'd love that!
All right, Shigechi, we
can't take your money.
What you were attempting
to do just now is honestly
no different than trying
to pay for our friendship.
But I...
I wasn't trying to do that!
Don't worry, I know you weren't.
But if you ask me, a friendship
is something you build over time.
All I was trying to do
was make some new friends.
Yeah, I get that.
And I know exactly how you feel.
We stand users have to stick together.
And so,
what do you say we all do a
nice round of team building and
strengthen our friendship with
a little business venture?
Huh?
Business venture? Yep.
Before you know it, us three
are gonna be stinking rich.
How do I stink?
I mean, lots of cash. Go with me here.
There's only so much money you can make
by picking up leftover change, right?
I know things have worked
out for you so far, but...
I have a much more lucrative
approach for harvests.
Oh?
You have a better plan
than picking up change?
This idea is legal, isn't it?
Yeah, there's nothing corrupt about it.
And no one will get hurt in the process.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
I'm liking what I'm hearing,
so what's your idea?
Well, that's where the
business part comes in.
And as compensation for coming
up with this marvelous proposal,
you give us half the profits.
The other half will go to you, Shigechi.
The three of us are
going to have to put our
heads together if we want
to pull this thing off.
But when all is said and done, we'll
finally get the payday we deserve.
That sounds good, but I'm confused.
What's my job supposed to be in all this?
Do you know what I'm holding?
It's a blue stamp. Right.
It comes with every 100
yen purchased from Kameyu.
You must have heard of
a chain this famous.
It's one of Eastern Japan's
biggest department stores.
And the best part about these stickers is
there are plenty of
people who just toss them.
Ooh.
But wait, there's more.
A 20 yen voucher from that
stationery store Meiwado.
And here's a voucher from CD shop Oscar.
Ten will get you 2,000
yen worth of merchandise.
Here's one from the cleaners.
Marching Kids Toy Store.
And this is a card from
Yotsuba Electronics.
Now pay attention,
because this is important.
With a place like Kamayu,
if you use this sticker,
you can get a little bit of cash back.
Oh, I see what you're getting at!
You're as amazing as ever, Josuke!
This is the best plan I've ever heard!
All right, everybody, go
into what you do best!
By themselves, these things are
as worthless as scraps of paper.
But, if you use Harvest to pick up the tens
of thousands of them lying around town,
well,
that's an entirely different story!
Got it!
This trash can!
Now that one!
Got it! Got it!
Look!
They just keep piling up!
I've lost count of them all!
Your stance the greatest ever!
Amazing Shigechi!
He he he he!
Another compliment!
A few are torn, but I'll fix
them with Shining Diamond!
Oh boy!
We must have thousands by now!
By the looks of it, it's
over a hundred thousand!
Yes!
This day belongs to the unbeatable trio!
Now let's go cash in!
Yeah!
So Josuke, what was that you
were saying about your pride?
You're such a smooth talker, it's
like you do this for a living!
Everyone's gonna be so happy in
the end, man, so it's all good!
Wow, I have friends now.
Friendship is the coolest.
Um, Okuyasu, I'm getting kinda nervous.
Do you think Josuke's gonna be okay?
Turning those thingies into
money sounds really tricky.
Relax, Shigechi.
Give Josuke a chance to work his magic.
It's Okuyasu and, uh, who is that?
Okuyasu!
Hey, Josuke!
How'd it go in there?
Did you manage to get our money?
They didn't tell you
to piss off, did they?
I found out that the CD shop and toy
store don't do cash back. That said,
we can exchange the coupons for about
40,000 yen worth of CDs and video games.
Yeah, yeah, that doesn't matter right now.
What about Kameyu?
Please tell me you were able to
get cash for the Kameyu stickers.
Not exactly.
Something unexpected came up last minute.
S-something unexpected?
We got 61,500 yen back instead!
Behold the genuine article, Shigechi!
Oh boy, oh boy, it's real money!
Real cash right before my very eyes!
This is like a dream come true!
You are the best!
Your harvest is amazing!
No other stand's ever come close to
its prowess! Really? You mean it?
You think it's amazing?
Oh, wow.
I don't usually get compliments.
You guys have been super nice.
I don't know what to say.
Do you really think I'm amazing?
Hey, have some faith
in yourself, Shigechi.
Yeah, you've got a power no one
else could ever dream of having.
You keep talking like that, and
I'll be a sobbing mess. All right.
Hey, doll face, I got a
fat stack of greenbacks.
Wanna have some fun?
Oh, yeah.
Okuyasu Josuke, I've
got something for you.
This is your cut, 10,000 large.
Hey, Shigechi, what the
hell is going on here?
The three of us are comrades in
business and life, aren't we?
I mean, you'd say that
we were friends, right?
Yeah, of course.
We're a team.
Well, the money I've gifted you is a
generous token of our new friendship.
Hold up a sec!
This isn't the amount
we agreed on, Shigechi!
You promised us that we'd get half of
whatever money we managed to scrape together!
Half of 61,500 yen is 30,750!
Really, I said that?
Nothing you're saying rings any bells!
Say what?!
Besides, it's not fair!
My harvest did all the work!
I don't remember you guys lifting
a single finger to help out!
The work was all me!
Maybe you two don't realize it,
but you're all talking no action!
Shut your damn mouth!
If Josuke hadn't come up with
the idea in the first place,
you never would have thought of
picking up those stupid stickers!
Now I would have come
up with it eventually.
I'm the amazing Shigechi, remember?
Wrong!
There's no way a cantaloupe head like you
would have thought of a plan like that!
Stop, Okuyasu!
Don't do something you'll regret later!
Just great.
The band's broken up already.
He was happy to give us a few thousand.
But the moment we ask
for a few ten thousands
now we're stepping over
the line all of a sudden.
He really doesn't mean any harm.
He just has the mentality of
a little kid no matter what we
say it's gonna feel like we're
duping him out of his money?
It sucks royally, but we should be
the adults here and call it a day.
We already got ten grand out
of it That's enough to get by
I guess if you put it that
way leaving is the best option
But Melon Head over there
really rubs me the wrong way.
You sure he's not
pulling a fast one on us?
No, Okuyasu.
And fighting's not going
to get us anywhere.
We have to handle this delicately.
I say we school him on how
mature adults do business.
Sly dog, you're still
England for the cash.
You fickle bastard, you.
Have I ever told you I
love that brain of yours?
You win, Shigechi.
We'll gladly accept
this amount as our cut.
Okuyasu.
You want something to drink?
Pick anyone you want,
I'm rich, so it's on me.
If you're treating, I'm drinking.
And you know, I think I
want some cowpiece water.
Go for it.
Josuke, how come you're
throwing those away?
Because they're nothing but worthless junk
now, just like year-end lottery tickets.
I remember telling
Shigechi to pick these up
when he was grabbing
all the other tickets.
You mean these losing New
Year's postcard lottery letters?
And just how would you know
if these were losing tickets?
That's an easy one.
No one's gonna throw away a
winning ticket, you dumbass.
You say that,
but I've heard that a lot of
people forget to check their
numbers and then end up missing
out on claiming their prizes.
If this wins, you have to promise me I can
take half of it for myself or wait clear.
Fine by me, half it is.
And if you win a sheet of stamps
instead of cold hard cash,
I'll let you keep that too.
Geez, Okuyasu,
I never realized how much you liked
those cheap little gambling games.
That one's no good.
How about this?
I didn't really think about it before,
but do you think I can collect lottery
prizes if I'm still in high school?
I don't see why you couldn't.
So long as you have your ID and name
stamp on you, it should be smooth sailing.
SG Group 121314.
Aw, man, that's lame.
It's just another dud.
Thought I had it this time. Guess not.
Uh, SG Group 1-2-1-3-1-4.
Hang on.
Hey, question.
If I happened to win the lottery by chance,
would I have to take it to the police?
You idiot.
Why would you turn it into them?
Harvest only picked up
what people threw away.
It's not stealing.
And besides that, unless you
were to somehow magically win,
it's a moot point, right?
But best of luck.
What?
This is SG Group 1, 2, 1, 3, 1, 4! Huh?
SG Group 1, 2, 1, 3, 1, 4?
It's SG Group 1, 2, 1, 3, 1, 4!
Whoa there, what are you
getting so worked up about?
Five million!
There's no doubt about it, I won!
Wait, are you kidding me?
This better not be a stupid joke.
That's great!
Oh yeah! Dream come true! Incredible!
We're the first to ever
experience this greatness!
Don't get ahead of yourself.
Settle down.
Let's just double check to
make sure you actually won.
SG Group 121314, prize 5 million yen.
Well, there you go.
It's hard to believe, but it's true.
If you hadn't found this
lottery ticket when you did,
it would have been off to the incinerator.
Look, it expires in a few days.
We have to get this to the bank.
And if they ask us a bunch of questions,
we'll tell them we bought
it fair and square.
and hope they believe us
so we can get the cash.
You good on that plan? You know it.
Lie and get the dough.
All right, we're going to
be 5 million yen richer!
Now, what should I buy first?
I know, I'll get some sick Italian shoes.
Then I'll buy a new designer suit
that complements my sexy physique.
After that, it's on to Tonio's
for his most expensive dish.
And of course, I'll have to
go someplace cool abroad.
I'm saving all my money!
Wow!
Talk about playing it safe!
My harvest did all the heavy lifting
while those two goofed around.
Every last yen of that
five million belongs to me.
I won't let them take it.
To the arms and the lips and the face of
the humic and the ball that I need to,
I want to.
Come and stand a little bit closer!
Breathe in and get a bit higher!
You'll never know what
hit you when I get to you!
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you?
Ooh, I want you!
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you?
Ooh, I've got to find out.